userzoom.com 2019-06-19

# UserZoom | Privacy Policy

**Please see below for information and links to our privacy policies for website visitors, study respondents, study creators and children's privacy:**

## Website Privacy Policy

 **Effective Date: June 5, 2019**

This privacy policy describes how UserZoom collects, handles, secures shares and uses the personal information you, as a visitor of our Website (“you” or “your”), provide through our Website located at [https://www.userzoom.com](https://www.userzoom.com/) (“Website”). It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy, unless we obtain your consent otherwise, or otherwise required by applicable law.

This privacy policy applies only to the information collected through visitors (i.e., users) of our Website. We provide certain products and services that may have supplementary privacy policies which explain in more detail our specific privacy practices in relation to those products and services. Unless otherwise noted, the Website and our products and services are provided by User Zoom, Inc. inside of the United States & Asia, and by UserZoom Ltd, UserZoom GmbH and UserZoom Technologies, Inc. outside of the United States, all of which are owned by UserZoom Technologies, Inc. (collectively, “UserZoom”, “we”, “our” or “us”).

Read more

## Privacy for Study Respondents

 **Effective Date: June 5, 2019**

This privacy policy describes how UserZoom collects, handles, secures, shares and uses the personal information and data you provide through the surveys conducted by our clients (“Client(s)”) using the services we provide. It also describes the choices available to you, as a study respondent (i.e., study participant), regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy, unless we obtain your consent otherwise, or otherwise required by applicable law. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged us.

Except where otherwise noted, this privacy policy applies to the products and services offered by us to you, the study participant. We refer to those products and services collectively as the “services” in this privacy policy. Some of our services may have supplementary privacy policies which explain in more detail our specific privacy practices in relation to those services. Unless otherwise noted, our services are provided by User Zoom, Inc. inside of the United States & Asia, and by UserZoom Ltd, UserZoom GmbH and UserZoom Technologies, Inc. outside of the United States, all of which are owned by UserZoom Technologies, Inc. (collectively, “UserZoom”, “we”, “our” or “us”).

Read more

## Privacy for Study Creators

 **Effective Date: June 5, 2019**

This privacy policy describes how UserZoom collects, handles, secures, shares and uses the personal information and data you provide to us through your use of our services. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you, as our client (“Client”) and study creator, can access and update this information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy, unless we obtain your consent otherwise, or otherwise required by applicable law. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which you, our Client, has engaged us.

Except where otherwise noted, this privacy policy applies to the products and services offered by us to you, the Client. We refer to those products and services collectively as the “services” in this privacy policy. Some of our services may have supplementary privacy policies which explain in more detail our specific privacy practices in relation to those services. Unless otherwise noted, our services are provided by User Zoom, Inc. inside of the United States & Asia, and by UserZoom Ltd, UserZoom GmbH and UserZoom Technologies, Inc. outside of the United States, all of which are owned by UserZoom Technologies, Inc. (collectively, “UserZoom”, “we”, “our” or “us”).

Read more

## [Children’s Privacy for Study Participants](https://www.userzoom.com/privacy-policy/coppa/)

 **Effective Date: March 23, 2017**

This privacy policy describes how we (“UserZoom”) collect and use the personal information and data you provide through our services. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

This privacy policy is a supplementary statement and explains in detail our specific privacy practices regarding participants 12 years old or younger and 13 to 17 years old in education. Unless otherwise noted, our services are provided by User Zoom, Inc. inside of the United States & Asia, and by UserZoom Ltd, UserZoom GmbH and UserZoom Technologies, Inc. outside the United States, all of which are owned by UserZoom Technologies, Inc.
